  import 'package:Gem_Quest/quiz.dart';

  List<QuizQuestion> mediumQuestions = [
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the birthstone for April?',
      answers: ['Ruby', 'Topaz', 'Diamond', 'Amethyst'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is typically red but can also appear in shades of pink and purple?',
      answers: ['Ruby', 'Spinel', 'Garnet', 'Tourmaline'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is often associated with the sea due to its blue-green color?',
      answers: ['Aquamarine', 'Emerald', 'Peridot', 'Turquoise'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is known for being brittle despite its hardness?',
      answers: ['Diamond', 'Topaz', 'Ruby', 'Sapphire'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the rarest color of a diamond?',
      answers: ['Yellow', 'Pink', 'Blue', 'Red'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What type of gemstone is often used to celebrate a 10th wedding anniversary?',
      answers: ['Sapphire', 'Diamond', 'Tourmaline', 'Emerald'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is often referred to as the "stone of the sun"?',
      answers: ['Sunstone', 'Citrine', 'Amber', 'Garnet'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What causes the green color in emeralds?',
      answers: ['Iron', 'Chromium', 'Manganese', 'Copper'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is known for its "cat’s eye" effect (chatoyancy)?',
      answers: ['Chrysoberyl', 'Moonstone', 'Tiger’s Eye', 'Tourmaline'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which country is the largest producer of opals?',
      answers: ['Brazil', 'South Africa', 'Australia', 'India'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    ),
  ];
